hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast I'm so excited
for this episode here this week you can
hear it in my voice we just got done
doing a two-day Mastermind with my
coaching Community my best clients we
had the most amazing time we also just
open the doors to a one-on-one coaching
opportunity it's over on my website
right now we only open this once a year
it's it's it's not cheap it's it's very
expensive uh but those that work with me
one-on-one they do get the most results
over all in their business and I'll tell
you if you have an opportunity to jump
in to work with me one-on-one maybe it's
next year I would love to work with you
that way otherwise in our client growth
accelerator we are having people that
are having breakthrough they're making
money in their businesses and they're
seeing scale happen and that's what we
do inside of our client growth
accelerator program is we create scale
inside of coaches course creators
Consultants businesses every single week
we Mentor you on the new nuances of what
it takes to be successful in your
business acquire more clients run ads
generate leads and most importantly
sales in your business overall and so
our client growth accelerator program if
you have a chance to join that as well
we'd love to see you in there um pay
attention we're testing out brand new
models right now of Evergreen marketing
and by the way it's working really great
I got an an early result to share with
you we got got eight new clients in the
last week off of our
Evergreen system and it was literally
just a test run that I
did kind of half half asked it a little
bit it wasn't perfect the ads were
weren't even set up right that didn't
even make them right but they worked and
so I'm like okay this is cool this is
working I can scale this I can make this
work we generated like 200 leads off of
a half built campaign and that's awesome
so I'm happy with this that's a 4%
conversion rate off of that too just off
of cold traffic um within a week so I'm
I'm super stoked on that we're going to
be teaching that to you in our
accelerator program I'm be sharing you
some of those insights as well on this
podcast and on my YouTube channel too so
stay plugged into the content that we
have let's dive in today on our topic
that we have what I want to do is I want
to talk about the
modalities of how we connect with new
clients where people come in and we talk
about this all the time when it comes to
our traffic sources how do we find new
clients how do we find new people the
system that we've pioneered inside of my
accelerator program is where we help you
find the right clients like where do
they exist right then we show you the
systems to promote to those people and
then once you've promoted to them the
most important part close them as sales
find promote close so finding that's the
market research part of the process
that's the part where we pick our topic
our Niche that's where we create our
landing pages we write our sales copy
then promoting is where we actually put
it out there and that's what I want to
talk about is the promote stage here and
how all of that works and
particularly the two aspects that I
think are most important for you in that
stage in your business which is the
initial hook that draws people in and
the call to action so there's a lot that
happens in between those two things but
I think that these are actually the most
important part of any sort of marketing
campaign any sort of piece of content
that you have in fact we have broken
down in our business every single piece
of content real estate marketing real
estate everything that we put out there
down to this and so like if I break this
down if I draw this on the Whiteboard
right now we got uh emails okay I send
emails out we got the
podcast we got YouTube we got social
media content YouTube's kind of a social
media channel we have ads we have our
landing pages and most importantly I
mean you could also throw ebooks in
there you can throw uh
PDFs but then also most importantly I I
would say
video
presentations okay and this is any sort
of video that's over 30 minutes long
that people would engage with our
YouTube kind of has some of this on
there but I'm talking about ones that
people have to register for ones that
people have to pay for that are part of
your Marketing System and one of the
biggest things that we encourage people
to do is to grow their coaching business
even when you're if you're building an
evergreen offer or you're doing it live
and by the way both work really well
live webinars work really well live
challenges work really well Evergreen
workshops work really well Evergreen
webinars work really well but it's about
what are you actually saying in those to
get the right people on them and then
get them to actually become a client of
yours so we're going to talk about what
it takes with these different modalities
right here in this episode by the end of
this you're going to have so much
Clarity on what to do and what to take
in your business to know how to get more
results okay so you need to have some
kind of an offer and that's the Baseline
to promoting your business and offers
are broken down into two categories we
have on one side our paid offer this
would be my coaching programs that I
have right here okay on the other side
we have what we call
freebies
slash low ticket okay and low ticket
ticket and then over here like this
would be mid ticket and high ticket this
is kind of how we have it broken down in
our business this is for
promotion this is for sales and
marketing this is cheap stuff over here
like when I talk cheap I'm talking 7 to
$27 that you're selling stuff for in
that now you could bump that up to 97 or
even 197 bucks I think that works even
297 I've seen people do that but for
most of our clients we go like with
freebies these are free webinars these
are free things that people sign up for
free video content and then we have paid
stuff that is very cheap very low cost
of Entry this could be whether it be a
VIP package during a free challenge or
it could be a paid Workshop of some kind
so what we get to do is we split this up
over here then over here we have our mid
ticket this is our $500 to $2500 price
product right here and this this is
still part of the value ladder the
Ascension model that we do and then High
ticket we're talking anything that is
like 7500 to 20
$25,000 right here
okay that's high ticket so this breaks
down into four levels we got free bees
at the bottom free content we got low
ticket 7 to 27 bucks we got mid ticket
500 to 2500 bucks which by the way is
reasonably affordable for the right
person and you can be super profitable
in your business and make seven figures
on$ 500 to
$2500 mid ticket
products but then you want to add a high
ticket access to it to increase your
margins to increase your profit ability
overall okay so when we're talking about
pricing that's the pricing that a lot of
the offers that we put out there are and
so we end up having basically two of
these just pick one like one over here
and one over here to start with for most
people
okay and if you never sold anything
before again I recommend going with
something that's free over here
something that's like $500 to $1,000 up
here that'll help you build your
confidence and then bump it up bump it
up to a th000 bump it up to
2500 and then as you sell that you're
able to sell higher ticket stuff like in
the in the10 to $25,000 range all right
so in
that we have to get specific in the hook
that draws people in to what our offer
is and we have to get very
explicit in the call to action that
we're making to people you know as
coaches mentors trainers course creators
Consultants we want people to be able to
make decisions as adults that are able
to make these decisions for themselves
and we want to trust that they can do
that but unfortunately most people don't
act that way
they can't be
trusted as much as I'd love for them to
be they not they can't be and so what we
have to do is we have to be the one to
tell people what to do you have to
explicitly tell people what action you
want them to take and so in any of these
modalities PDFs ebooks emails podcasts
YouTube channel social media content
advertising landing
pages video
presentations you need something that's
going to pull people in and this is a
location that you're taking somebody to
I want you to imagine that each of these
is like a storefront and they're
separate storefronts so you have a brand
that you're building your personal brand
these are different storefronts to your
personal brand these are different
modalities of how somebody engages with
you and I'll tell you this people can
only engage with one of these modalities
at a time so that's key to
understand somebody can only read your
PDF they can only read one email they
can only listen to One podcast at a time
they can only watch one YouTube video at
a time with you they can only watch one
social media content at a time with you
they can only watch one ad they can only
read one Landing or sales page with you
at a time they can only watch one long
form video
presentation at a time
and so what we're doing is we're taking
people to a
place physically in cyberspace where
they're spending time with us and
they're getting to know us and this is
what is the nurture
process and
so let's clean up the Whiteboard here
I'm going to show you something here
when people first come in with you they
are on a journey there's a customer and
client Journey that they go on this is
zero knowledge about you they don't know
who you are from Adam and the problem is
most people are trying to sell over here
the chances of you closing a sale with
somebody over here virtually none you
have to nurture the
relationship and build up what we call
the
klt
bank the klt bank is this you build no
like and Trust they know you they like
you and they trust
you when somebody first meets you on the
internet they have no clue about you
they know you maybe now they're getting
to know you and I liken this to a
dating
relationship you know when when a couple
meets they're not going to get married
on the first interaction
and yet in our businesses we're
expecting that to happen if we're if
we're operating from a place of scarcity
lack mindset the way that most coaches
do but that's not you and you're
listening to this right now because I
because you are somebody that is
operating at a higher level so your goal
and if you're watching this right now is
to know how to build that no like and
trust and I think you're starting to
understand that so all of those
different modalities that we talked
about in the last whiteboard paper are
what builds that no like and trust but
we're also moving people to multiple
touch
points here's a here's a a webinar okay
here's an email here's a YouTube
video here's a social media post here's
a here's a a workshop here's another
presentation and now the person is ready
to become a paid client of yours they
weren't over here but as you continue to
nurture that relationship they become
ready because that no like and trust is
built and so what we do is we figure out
who are we working with who is this
client and we start speaking directly to
them about a specific problem or area in
their life and business they need
solved chances are that your potential
clients have something that's bugging
them that they want fixed and that thing
that they need fixed fits perfectly into
the framework of what you do and so when
you create a social media post you want
to draw people in with something that is
bold audacious and sometimes scary that
gets their
attention that's what we call a hook and
that hook gets people to
understand that it's for them people are
being inundated with messages all the
time how many you have looked at your
email inbox this morning there are way
too many emails in it maybe you found an
email with this video in there and
you're thankful you found it right and
you're and you're going to whitelist all
my emails and make sure that you open
every single one as they come in right
but because of that you you know that
you ignore emails as they come in and so
do your prospects there are so many
videos on YouTube you don't know which
ones to watch there are so many social
media posts we scroll through social
media we are in inundated
with messaging
constantly and so what allows us to rise
above that is what we call supernormal
stimulus supernormal stimulus is
something that grabs somebody's
attention generally it might be outside
of the realm of what normal human
communication operates in and that's how
a hook works so a hook grabs somebody's
attention initially and then they dive
in deeper with you to understand
understand okay what is the message that
you have to
share so you want to look at whether
you're making a social media post you
want some kind of a hook that grabs
somebody's attention could be something
that's written in an absolute or even
polarizing extreme way some kind of an
absolute statement that then you can
break down further what the explanation
of that is and then you get to call
people to action and so at the end of
each touch point you want some kind of a
call to action and if you're doing this
properly every touch point you have is
calling somebody to action to the next
touch Point within a week or
so and this is why within about 21 days
of interaction you can take somebody
from virtually not knowing who you are
and within two within three weeks you
can get them to actually pay you up to
$25,000 we've done it we've helped our
clients do it and you can as well and
and and by the way these are people that
love what they purchased they leave rave
reviews they love what we're doing like
our clients that we get to work with all
the
time and so what you got to start doing
is you got to start getting more
specific about who you help you start to
get more specific about the outcome that
you can deliver at each touch point you
talk about the outcome that
specifically is connected to what the
person that you help wants and then you
direct directly call them to action to
do something you don't just leave it
open-ended no open-ended communication
and that's something that I really would
encourage you with no open-ended
communication inside of every
interaction there's some sort of a Next
Step that you want people to
take you know about 5 years ago we
didn't do this and and and now because
of the world that we live in if you
don't you're you're missing ing the boat
completely I used to hear people and I
still hear people today they're like
well I don't want to be too salesy I
don't want to be promoting too much can
I tell you this when you give a call to
action at the end of a really powerful
piece of content it doesn't feel that
way because it's kind of like you're
giving so much value away for free and
it's sponsored by this offer that you're
making have you ever listen to a podcast
that's sponsored by something what you
end up doing as a coach or course
Creator is you are self-sponsored I am
self-sponsored on this podcast and we
have no sponsors that are outside but my
business is paying for me to be able to
create this podcast and give it away for
free to people it's self-sponsored that
way and so when we create content we are
self telling people about what the
action step that we want them to take is
I would love to see you in my client
growth accelerator coaching
program I'd love to see you join me on
one of my live or free trainings that we
have you can find in the description
below this video you can find them on
the homepage of my website you'll see
ads that are on social media you can go
look on my social media channels they're
everywhere I tell you about them in
every post now that we're doing making
offers consistently and the person who
makes more offers more often more
consistently is the one that succeeds
and makes the kind of finances that they
want in their business and so if you're
looking to actually grow your business
if you're looking to actually create the
kind of business that you want you have
to start getting consistent about your
messaging who you help talking about
very specific
outcomes and when you create your offers
we're taking one piece of what our
system is and dialing that in into that
and then we're leading people to take
action in some way
with that offer for the next step that
we want them to go into now in our
Mastermind this week we broke down how
this translates into all of our clients
businesses we did live hot seats where
we worked with them on how to translate
all of this into their ads their emails
their marketing their landing pages and
their presentations and if you're
somebody that wants to work with us in
that I'd love to see you in our
accelerator
program leave a comment below as well
share this with somebody this podcast is
a res resource for you that you can use
to learn how to grow your business and
how to grow your life and make more
money in it so listen this is jerem
kowsky signing off on this episode if
you apply what I talk about on this
podcast you will start to see changes in
your life and business we'll talk soon
have a good one bye
[Music]
[Applause]